{
    "subject": "resource/James_Newton_Howard",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Musicians_from_Los_Angeles,_California",
    "human_readable": "The subject of James Newton Howard is Musicians from Los Angeles, California.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9032295346260071,
            "question": "Is James Newton Howard a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8308020234107971,
            "question": "Where is James Newton Howard from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8116461634635925,
            "question": "Which city is associated with James Newton Howard's musical career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.698536217212677,
            "question": "Where might you find James Newton Howard's music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6329349875450134,
            "question": "What profession does James Newton Howard have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5793010592460632,
            "question": "Can you name other famous musicians from Los Angeles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5777624249458313,
            "question": "What is James Newton Howard known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47270095348358154,
            "question": "What kind of work does James Newton Howard likely do?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33666878938674927,
            "question": "What state is Los Angeles, California in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23080216348171234,
            "question": "Is Los Angeles a major center for the music industry?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of James Newton Howard is Musicians from Los Angeles, California.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6927_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What state is Los Angeles, California in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6927_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of work does James Newton Howard likely do?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6927_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is James Newton Howard known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6927_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6927_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6927_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6927_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6927_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6927_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6927_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6927_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6927_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6927_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6927_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about James Newton Howard's career as a musician and his origins in Los Angeles, California. Therefore, the statement that he is a \"Musician from Los Angeles, California\" is supported by the context provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}